<resources xmlns:xliff="rn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2">
    <string name="app_name">Messtex</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="email"><u>info@messtex.de</u></string>
    <string name="scan_help"><u>Where can I find the reading code? Click here</u></string>
    <string name="skip"><u>Skip</u></string>
    <string name="title_activity_onboarding">OnboardingActivity</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="scan">Start</string>
    <string name="more">More</string>
    <string name="contact">Contact:</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="about_title">Through years of experience, we have determined the importance of modernizing our professional field. For you as a tenant, for you as a property owner, and for our country and our earth.</string>
    <string name="about_paragraph_one">We want to digitize every manual reading in Germany! And thus make reading as easy and convenient as possible for everyone involved. Especially in times of digitization and the permanent lack of time, it is essential that we simplify things in this industry as well.</string>
    <string name="about_subtitle">The digital meter reading input, which you can easily record yourself with messtex, saves you a lot of time. The advantages are clear</string>
    <string name="about_bulletpoint_one">By reading with the Messtex app, you no longer have to waste vacation days on manual readings by service technicians</string>
    <string name="about_bulletpoint_two">Waiting for the service technicians becomes unnecessary</string>
    <string name="about_bulletpoint_three">Entering your home by foreign service technicians who have a lot of contact with other people and households becomes unnecessary - especially in these times in which we live with COVID-19</string>
    <string name="about_bulletpoint_four">We protect our environment together, because the many trips for first and second appointments, sometimes even third appointments become obsolete</string>
    <string name="about_bulletpoint_five">We save a lot of mail traffic and paper if you choose our digital reminder service for meter reading</string>
    <string name="about_paragraph_two">With the help of our partners, we have developed a unique system with which you can easily, time- and cost-efficiently perform your own meter reading. In designing our app, we placed great emphasis on making it easy and intuitive to use, so that truly everyone can benefit from our renewal</string>
    <string name="about_box_title">We are a contact you can trust. We are at your side in all situations and are always available for you.</string>
    <string name="principles_title">What makes us the best choice?</string>
    <string name="prinicples_subtitle">At Messtex, we have made it our mission to modernize the meter reading sector and to reform the market together with our partners and customers. The 21st century has already brought us many things: digitization is continuously overhauling and improving existing legacy systems and giving them a new lease of life. We are getting on this bandwagon of innovation and making the vision of revolutionizing the meter reading sector! To do this, we have set ourselves strict principles by which we live and act every day:</string>
    <string name="prinicples_bulletpoint_title_one">Living sustainability.</string>
    <string name="prinicples_bulletpoint_title_two">Anyone can be innovative.</string>
    <string name="prinicples_bulletpoint_title_three">Simply simple.</string>
    <string name="prinicples_bulletpoint_paragraph_one">By digitizing the process of recording heating and water costs, we are making a valuable contribution to the environment. In this way, we reduce our ecological footprint and take responsibility.</string>
    <string name="prinicples_bulletpoint_paragraph_two">Innovation means progress. We want to shape this progress so that everyone can follow it from home.</string>
    <string name="prinicples_bulletpoint_paragraph_three">We would like to make the recording of heating and water costs as simple and convenient as possible for you. With no waiting for the service technician, no formal clean-up, and no invasion of your privacy.</string>
    <string name="code_reading_title">Reading code</string>
    <string name="code_reading_subtitle">Please enter the six digit code from your informational letter.</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="contact_title">Get in touch with us</string>
    <string name="email_title">Email</string>
    <string name="contact_details">Contact details</string>
    <string name="contact_details_subtitle">In order to assign your details correctly, we need your contact details:</string>
    <string name="first_name">First name*</string>
    <string name="surname">Surname*</string>
    <string name="contact_copy">Please send me the overview as an email copy</string>
    <string name="newsletter">May we inform you from now on simply and quickly by e-mail about news?</string>
    <string name="receiveViaEmail">May we remind you in the future per E-Mail instead of post letter about your meter reading?</string>
    <string name="phone_number">Phone number</string>
    <string name="address">Address</string>
    <string name="street">Street*</string>
    <string name="house_number">House number*</string>
    <string name="plz">PLZ*</string>
    <string name="city">City*</string>
    <string name="floor">Floor (optional)</string>
    <string name="required_fields">* Required fields</string>
    <string name="name">Name*</string>
    <string name="subject">Subject</string>
    <string name="message">Message</string>
    <string name="send">Send</string>
    <string name="your_copy">Your copy</string>
    <string name="home_title">Welcome to Messtex</string>
    <string name="home_subtitle">Record your meter readings. Easy, quick and without an appointment.</string>
    <string name="start_reading">Start reading</string>
    <string name="co2_title">Help us protect the environment.</string>
    <string name="co2_subtitle">kilograms of CO₂ have already\nbeen saved together!</string>
    <string name="tips_and_tricks">Tips and Tricks</string>
    <string name="tips_and_tricks_subtitle">Here you will find useful tips for your everyday life.</string>
    <string name="show_more">Show more</string>
    <string name="get_in_contact">Get in contact with us</string>
    <string name="share_the_app">Contact us</string>
    <string name="manual_input_title">Manual input</string>
    <string name="manual_input_subtitle">Now enter the reading of your meter:</string>
    <string name="counter_number">Counter number</string>
    <string name="counter_type">Counter type</string>
    <string name="reading_date">Reading date</string>
    <string name="report_comments_or_defects">Report comments or defects</string>
    <string name="enter_manually">Enter manually</string>
    <string name="meter_number">Instructions for reading:</string>
    <string name="meter_reading">Meter reading:</string>
    <string name="more_about_messtex">More about Messtex</string>
    <string name="more_about_subtitle">We want to digitize every manual reading in Germany!</string>
    <string name="contact_form">Contact Form</string>
    <string name="privacy">Privacy</string>
    <string name="imprint">Imprint</string>
    <string name="restart_onboarding">Restart Onboarding</string>
    <string name="share_app">Share App</string>
    <string name="onboarding_title_one">Digital reading</string>
    <string name="onboarding_title_two">Without appointment with the Messtex App</string>
    <string name="onboarding_title_three">Cost effective for our environment</string>
    <string name="onboarding_subtitle_three">Together we protect our environment, take responsibility and you save money.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_subtitle_one">Enter your water and heating cost recordings digitally \&amp; comfortably from home.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_subtitle_two">All this without waiting, without formal cleanup and without foreign intrusion into your private sphere.</string>
    <string name="reading_steps_title">Start reading</string>
    <string name="reading_steps_subtitle">Please send us the following meter readings:</string>
    <string name="submit_meter_readings">Submit meter readings</string>
    <string name="success_title">Meter readings successfully transmitted</string>
    <string name="success_subtitle">Thank you %1$s for your contribution. Your data has been successfully transmitted. With your help we were able to save 3g of CO₂.</string>
    <string name="learn_more">Learn more</string>
    <string name="language">Language</string>
    <string name="imprint_title">Information according to § 5 TMG</string>
    <string name="represented_by">Represented by:</string>
    <string name="sales_tax_paragraph">Sales tax identification number according to §27a Umsatzsteuergesetz: DE337739004.</string>
    <string name="sales_tax_title">Sales tax ID:</string>
    <string name="responsibility_title">Responsible for the content according to § 55 Abs. 2 RStV:</string>
    <string name="responsibility_paragraph">BRIGHTDOCK Llc, Croatia, Rijeka (City of Rijeka) Nikole Tesle 9</string>
    <string name="disclaimer_paragraph">Despite careful control of the content, we do not assume any liability for the content of external links. The operators of the linked pages are solely responsible for their content.</string>
    <string name="disclaimer">Disclaimer</string>
    <string name="modal_title">Counter reading explanation</string>
    <string name="email_required">Email*</string>
    <string name="message_required">Message*</string>
    <string name="learn_more_about">learn more about</string>
    <string name="success_card_subtitle">Check out our tips and tricks discover more from the Messtex world</string>
    <string name="success_card_title">Thank you, everything is done!</string>
    <string name="contact_form_title">Get in contact with us</string>
    <string name="contact_form_subtitle">Get in touch with us and describe your concern.</string>
    <string name="imprint_contact">Phone: 0151/41888186\nE-Mail: info@messtex.de</string>
    <string name="contact_and_contract_data">Contact and contract data</string>
    <string name="change">Change</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="date">Reading date: %1$s</string>
    <string name="counter_number_explanation">Please scan the counter:<br />%1$s, %2$s No. %3$s</string>
    <string name="legal">General terms of use</string>
    <string name="messtex_environment">Messtex &amp; Environment</string>
    <string name="save_heating_costs">Save heating costs</string>
    <string name="save_water">Save water</string>
    <string name="confirmation_text">Do you want to send your data? Changes are not possible after sending.</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="meter_type_text">Please choose your meter type?</string>
    <string name="messtex_amp_numweltschutz">Messtex &amp; Environment</string>
    <string name="saving_water">Saving water</string>
    <string name="water_tip_paragraph_one">Water is a very precious commodity that we should use sustainably. In the following, we will show you a few tips with which you can quickly and effectively reduce your water consumption.</string>
    <string name="water_tip_title_one">In the bathroom and in the laundry:</string>
    <string name="water_tip_one_one">Your morning shower is a good place to start for more sustainability, as it usually consumes between 6 and 45 gallons of water per minute. Try to reduce consumption to less than 5 minutes per shower. This can reduce your water use by up to 20 percent.</string>
    <string name="water_tip_one_two">If short showers are not an option for you, switch to an economical showerhead. A standard showerhead uses 15 to 25 gallons of water per minute. If you switch to a three-star energy- efficient showerhead, you can reduce your water consumption by about 40 percent. Before you buy one model, remember to check out the features and benefits to find out how many gallons of water per minute it uses.</string>
    <string name="water_tip_one_three">This will reduce the amount of water used per flush. A simple DIY solution is to weigh down two plastic bottles with pebbles or sand, fill the bottles with water, screw on the lids, and place them securely in your toilet tank, away from the controls.</string>
    <string name="water_tip_one_four">Put some food coloring in the tank. If the color begins to appear in the bowl without flushing within half an hour, you have a leak that should be repaired immediately.</string>
    <string name="water_tip_one_five">Since 90 percent of your washing machine\'s electricity consumption goes to heating the water you can save by using colder water.</string>
    <string name="water_tip_title_two">In the kitchen:</string>
    <string name="water_tip_two_one">You can significantly reduce your water consumption by repairing leaks in the bathroom and kitchen. A dripping faucet with only one drop per second wastes over 6000 gallons of water every year. So, fix those leaks and start saving today!</string>
    <string name="water_tip_two_two">If you have two sinks, fill one with soapy water and the other with rinse water. If you have only one sink, place the washed dishes on a dish rack and rinse them with a sprayer or a pot full of hot water.</string>
    <string name="water_tip_two_three">You\'ll use less hot water by running your dishwasher only when it\'s actually full and by choosing shorter, economical rinse cycles. If you\'re worried that the shorter cycles won\'t get your dishes clean enough, you can also rinse them with cold water before putting them in the machine.</string>
    <string name="water_tip_title_three">In the garden:</string>
    <string name="water_tip_three_one">Purchase timers for your watering systems and be careful not to over water. This can help not only your water consumption, but also your plants. Once your plants get used to a lot of water, they won\'t root as deeply and will be weaker as a result.</string>
    <string name="water_tip_three_two">With a rain barrel, you can easily and effectively reduce your water consumption.</string>
    <string name="water_tip_paragraph_two">We hope we were able to help you with a few of our tips! There are of course countless other ways to save water, but with these tips you are making a good start.</string>
    <string name="heat_tip_title">Saving heating costs</string>
    <string name="heat_tip_paragraph_one">Water is a very precious commodity that we should use sustainably. In the following, we will show you a few tips with which you can quickly and effectively reduce your water consumption.</string>
    <string name="heat_tip_one_one_title">Take advantage of the warmth of the sun:</string>
    <string name="heat_tip_one_one">During the day, open the curtains on your south-facing windows to let the sunlight can heat up your house or apartment naturally. Additionally, if you plant deciduous trees on the south side of your home, the trees will allow light and warmth into your windows in the winter and cast shade in the summer.</string>
    <string name="heat_tip_one_two_title">Cover old windows:</string>
    <string name="heat_tip_one_two">Install tight-fitting, insulating curtains or blinds on windows that feel cold after weather adjustment. Find out about other window treatments and coverings that can improve Improve energy efficiency.</string>
    <string name="heat_tip_one_three_title">Adjust the temperature:</string>
    <string name="heat_tip_one_three">Use your thermostat to regulate the temperature to a comfortable, but rather lower temperature. If you sleep at night or are not in the house, it is recommended to set your thermostat as low as possible. Doing so can save you up to 10% on heating and/or cooling costs. If you have a heat pump, you should maintain a moderate setting or use a programmable thermostat that has been specifically designed.</string>
    <string name="heat_tip_one_four_title">Find and seal leaks:</string>
    <string name="heat_tip_one_four">Seal air leaks near penetrations for ductwork and gaps around chimneys and recessed lights in insulated ceilings. Add sealant or caulk to seal air leaks at leaking doors and windows.</string>
    <string name="heat_tip_one_five_title">Schedule maintenance for your heating system:</string>
    <string name="heat_tip_one_five_A">For furnaces and heat pumps:<br />Replace your filter once a month or as needed.</string>
    <string name="heat_tip_one_five_B">Wood and pellet heaters:<br />Clean the flue regularly and clean the inside of the unit regularly with a wire brush to ensure your home is heated efficiently.</string>
    <string name="heat_tip_one_six_title">Reduce heat loss from the flue:</string>
    <string name="heat_tip_one_six">Keep your fireplace damper closed when there is no fire burning. Keeping the damper open is like opening a window wide in the winter, this allows warm air to go directly into the chimney. When using the fireplace, reduce heat loss by opening the dampers at the bottom of the firebox (if any) or opening the nearest window slightly - about an inch - and closing the doors leading into the room. If you never use your fireplace, plug and seal the chimney flue.</string>
    <string name="heat_tip_one_seven_title">Lower your water heating costs:</string>
    <string name="heat_tip_one_seven">Turn down the temperature of your water heater to the warm setting (120°F). Not only will you save energy, but you\'ll also avoid scalding your hands.</string>
    <string name="environment_tip_title"><![CDATA[Messtex & environmental protection]]></string>
    <string name="environment_tip_paragraph_one">To this day, all service technicians are on the road every day by car to take the annual readings in all apartments in Germany. Each apartment must be visited at least once. If a resident is not at home at the first appointment, the technician often has to come a second time and sometimes even a third time.<br />On some days, a single technician thus travels several hundred kilometers to perform his assignments. These kilometers not only increase your additional costs in the final bill, but also increase the CO2 emissions immeasurably.</string>
    <string name="environment_tip_paragraph_two">In the following example calculation, we take the mileage values from the logbook of a service technician in January 2021 and calculate how much CO2 could have been saved with a reading via our Messtex app:</string>
    <string name="environment_tip_paragraph_three">The technician drove 2,835 kilometers in January to read meters in his region of responsibility. meter readings. In our calculation, we take the consumption values of a new gasoline engine. This puts us at 559.6 kg of CO2 in the month of January. Let\'s assume that the technician drives the same route in 11 out of 12 months. This puts the CO2 consumption at an incredible 6,155.6 kg.</string>
    <string name="environment_tip_paragraph_four">To give you a comparison, the average per capita CO2 consumption in Germany is 7,900 kg per year. The service technician would have achieved this almost through his work trips alone, thus driving up the average consumption enormously.</string>
    <string name="environment_tip_paragraph_five">By reading with the Messtex app, all these trips are saved and together with you we protect our environment and take responsibility!</string>
    <string name="water_tip_one_one_title">Shower a little shorter:</string>
    <string name="water_tip_one_two_title">Install low-flow showerheads:</string>
    <string name="water_tip_one_three_title">Put in a water-efficient toilet flush:</string>
    <string name="water_tip_one_four_title">Check your toilet for leaks:</string>
    <string name="water_tip_one_five_title">Wash your clothes with colder water:</string>
    <string name="water_tip_two_one_title">Shower a little shorter:</string>
    <string name="water_tip_two_two_title">Install low-flow showerheads:</string>
    <string name="water_tip_two_three_title">Put in a water-efficient toilet flush:</string>
    <string name="water_tip_three_one_title">Shower a little shorter:</string>
    <string name="water_tip_three_two_title">Install low-flow showerheads:</string>
    <string name="reading_time_2_1_2_minutes">(Reading time 2 1/2 minutes)</string>
    <string name="reading_time_3_minutes">(Reading time 3 minutes)</string>
    <string name="reading_time_1_2_minutes">(Reading time 1 - 2 minutes)</string>
</resources>